{"Question": "DAD + ADD = ERA", "Answer": "626 + 266 = 892"}
{"Question": "DAD + ADD = ALLY", "Answer": "818 + 188 = 1006"}
{"Question": "EYE + YES = ARMY", "Answer": "686 + 862 = 1548"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODD = DEEP", "Answer": "191 + 811 = 1002"}
{"Question": "EYE + FEE = EASY", "Answer": "121 + 911 = 1032"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODD = DROP", "Answer": "181 + 911 = 1092"}
{"Question": "EYE + FEE = ALLY", "Answer": "484 + 744 = 1228"}
{"Question": "DAD + ODD = TOO", "Answer": "656 + 266 = 922"}
{"Question": "EYE + SEE = YES", "Answer": "696 + 266 = 962"}
{"Question": "EYE + SEE = STAY", "Answer": "868 + 188 = 1056"}
{"Question": "EYE + FEE = FALL", "Answer": "878 + 188 = 1066"}
{"Question": "EYE + FEE = FUEL", "Answer": "898 + 188 = 1086"}
{"Question": "EYE + FEE = YEAH", "Answer": "818 + 988 = 1806"}
{"Question": "TOO + OUT = BOMB", "Answer": "922 + 279 = 1201"}
{"Question": "ADD + DNA = BEAN", "Answer": "455 + 594 = 1049"}
{"Question": "ADD + DNA = ONTO", "Answer": "477 + 724 = 1201"}
{"Question": "ADD + DNA = ALLY", "Answer": "188 + 821 = 1009"}
{"Question": "ADD + DNA = ARAB", "Answer": "188 + 831 = 1019"}
{"Question": "EYE + HEY = AREA", "Answer": "292 + 729 = 1021"}
{"Question": "EYE + HEY = HIGH", "Answer": "838 + 183 = 1021"}
{"Question": "FEE + EGG = FUEL", "Answer": "188 + 899 = 1087"}
{"Question": "EYE + SEA = EASE", "Answer": "181 + 910 = 1091"}
{"Question": "EYE + SET = EASY", "Answer": "181 + 917 = 1098"}
{"Question": "EYE + BED = BABY", "Answer": "828 + 184 = 1012"}
{"Question": "EYE + TEA = THAT", "Answer": "848 + 183 = 1031"}
{"Question": "EGG + GAP = EDGE", "Answer": "188 + 893 = 1081"}
{"Question": "TOO + OWE = WELL", "Answer": "388 + 812 = 1200"}
{"Question": "EYE + BED = YELL", "Answer": "818 + 982 = 1800"}
{"Question": "ALL + LEG = ELSE", "Answer": "988 + 813 = 1801"}
{"Question": "DAD + AID = ARAB", "Answer": "818 + 198 = 1016"}
{"Question": "DAD + AND = AIDE", "Answer": "919 + 179 = 1098"}
{"Question": "DAD + AID = NINE", "Answer": "575 + 735 = 1310"}
{"Question": "NOW + OWN = WHO", "Answer": "516 + 165 = 681"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALL = ARAB", "Answer": "818 + 199 = 1017"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALL = AREA", "Answer": "919 + 122 = 1041"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALL = AIDE", "Answer": "919 + 177 = 1096"}
{"Question": "MOM + OFF = FEE", "Answer": "434 + 388 = 822"}
{"Question": "WHO + HOW = OWE", "Answer": "348 + 483 = 831"}
{"Question": "TEA + EAT = MATH", "Answer": "752 + 527 = 1279"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALL = THAT", "Answer": "272 + 799 = 1071"}
{"Question": "TEA + EAT = BAKE", "Answer": "572 + 725 = 1297"}
{"Question": "NOW + OWN = GENE", "Answer": "678 + 786 = 1464"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALL = FLEE", "Answer": "878 + 766 = 1644"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALL = EASE", "Answer": "979 + 722 = 1701"}
{"Question": "DAD + ALL = DEEP", "Answer": "181 + 822 = 1003"}
{"Question": "POP + ODD = PIPE", "Answer": "181 + 833 = 1014"}
{"Question": "TEA + EAT = TIME", "Answer": "187 + 871 = 1058"}
{"Question": "NOW + OWN = AWAY", "Answer": "483 + 834 = 1317"}
{"Question": "ASK + SEA = SELL", "Answer": "913 + 109 = 1022"}
{"Question": "EAT + AGE = AREA", "Answer": "912 + 179 = 1091"}
{"Question": "DAD + ASK = AIDS", "Answer": "919 + 178 = 1097"}
{"Question": "MOM + OUT = AUTO", "Answer": "757 + 528 = 1285"}
{"Question": "TEN + EAT = RARE", "Answer": "769 + 647 = 1416"}
{"Question": "DRY + RED = DOOR", "Answer": "187 + 821 = 1008"}
{"Question": "RED + EAR = RIDE", "Answer": "187 + 891 = 1078"}
{"Question": "DRY + RED = YEAR", "Answer": "781 + 867 = 1648"}
{"Question": "SIR + ITS = REST", "Answer": "981 + 809 = 1790"}
{"Question": "DAD + AGE = GANG", "Answer": "989 + 812 = 1801"}
{"Question": "ADD + MAD = ARMY", "Answer": "177 + 917 = 1094"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAD = ARAB", "Answer": "199 + 819 = 1018"}
{"Question": "ODD + GOD = AGO", "Answer": "211 + 321 = 532"}
{"Question": "EGG + LEG = GAME", "Answer": "211 + 821 = 1032"}
{"Question": "EGG + LEG = ALL", "Answer": "566 + 256 = 822"}
{"Question": "ADD + SAD = BOSS", "Answer": "788 + 678 = 1466"}
{"Question": "EGG + LEG = GIRL", "Answer": "811 + 281 = 1092"}
{"Question": "ADD + BAD = BEER", "Answer": "822 + 182 = 1004"}
{"Question": "ODD + NOD = NINE", "Answer": "833 + 183 = 1016"}
{"Question": "EGG + LEG = LAKE", "Answer": "844 + 184 = 1028"}
{"Question": "SEE + USE = ODDS", "Answer": "844 + 384 = 1228"}
{"Question": "ODD + GOD = GENE", "Answer": "855 + 185 = 1040"}
{"Question": "ALL + SAD = AIDS", "Answer": "144 + 915 = 1059"}
{"Question": "ADD + EAT = AREA", "Answer": "177 + 914 = 1091"}
{"Question": "ADD + EAR = RARE", "Answer": "388 + 931 = 1319"}
{"Question": "PER + ERA = WRAP", "Answer": "842 + 426 = 1268"}
{"Question": "TEA + EAR = RATE", "Answer": "954 + 541 = 1495"}
{"Question": "EGG + SEA = BASE", "Answer": "622 + 864 = 1486"}
{"Question": "SEA + EAR = RARE", "Answer": "865 + 651 = 1516"}
{"Question": "ODD + HOT = DATA", "Answer": "711 + 379 = 1090"}
{"Question": "HER + ERA = ARAB", "Answer": "674 + 741 = 1415"}
{"Question": "EGG + TEA = GATE", "Answer": "811 + 987 = 1798"}
{"Question": "SKI + KID = SEEK", "Answer": "182 + 826 = 1008"}
{"Question": "EGG + NET = NINE", "Answer": "833 + 185 = 1018"}
{"Question": "EGG + BET = BITE", "Answer": "855 + 183 = 1038"}
{"Question": "TOO + ITS = COST", "Answer": "855 + 683 = 1538"}
{"Question": "EGG + BED = BAKE", "Answer": "866 + 182 = 1048"}
{"Question": "ADD + TAX = TEXT", "Answer": "866 + 185 = 1051"}
{"Question": "EGG + BET = TUBE", "Answer": "877 + 581 = 1458"}
{"Question": "ALL + DAY = DEAD", "Answer": "899 + 182 = 1081"}
{"Question": "ACT + CAT = TALL", "Answer": "391 + 931 = 1322"}
{"Question": "SUE + USE = MENU", "Answer": "584 + 854 = 1438"}
{"Question": "SON + OWN = ODDS", "Answer": "814 + 194 = 1008"}
{"Question": "RED + END = EARN", "Answer": "914 + 184 = 1098"}
{"Question": "WHY + HEY = HERE", "Answer": "915 + 105 = 1020"}
{"Question": "OWN + WIN = WILL", "Answer": "916 + 106 = 1022"}
{"Question": "TOE + ONE = OPEN", "Answer": "918 + 168 = 1086"}
{"Question": "BET + EAT = TUBE", "Answer": "821 + 261 = 1082"}
{"Question": "BAD + AID = DATA", "Answer": "921 + 281 = 1202"}
{"Question": "END + NOD = ONE", "Answer": "628 + 298 = 926"}
{"Question": "LET + EAT = ALL", "Answer": "246 + 476 = 722"}
{"Question": "EAT + ART = FREE", "Answer": "854 + 534 = 1388"}
{"Question": "TEA + ERA = RATE", "Answer": "763 + 613 = 1376"}
{"Question": "EAR + AIR = FREE", "Answer": "864 + 624 = 1488"}
{"Question": "FLY + LAY = ALL", "Answer": "268 + 698 = 966"}
{"Question": "FAR + AIR = ROOF", "Answer": "271 + 731 = 1002"}
{"Question": "EAT + ACT = TREE", "Answer": "271 + 751 = 1022"}
{"Question": "EAT + ACT = CITE", "Answer": "879 + 719 = 1598"}
{"Question": "BET + EAT = TALL", "Answer": "581 + 841 = 1422"}
{"Question": "HIS + ITS = HOST", "Answer": "182 + 842 = 1024"}
{"Question": "ACT + CUT = ALLY", "Answer": "183 + 823 = 1006"}
{"Question": "FLY + LAY = FEEL", "Answer": "184 + 824 = 1008"}
{"Question": "BET + EAT = BITE", "Answer": "184 + 864 = 1048"}
{"Question": "OWN + WIN = KNOW", "Answer": "584 + 874 = 1458"}
{"Question": "EAT + ACT = CALL", "Answer": "985 + 815 = 1800"}
{"Question": "EAT + ART = EVER", "Answer": "186 + 826 = 1012"}
{"Question": "WHO + HER = HERE", "Answer": "918 + 102 = 1020"}
{"Question": "DNA + NOR = ARAB", "Answer": "751 + 563 = 1314"}
{"Question": "CEO + ERA = RACE", "Answer": "872 + 715 = 1587"}
{"Question": "BED + EAT = DATA", "Answer": "281 + 809 = 1090"}
{"Question": "HER + EAT = RARE", "Answer": "481 + 837 = 1318"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAD = ALL", "Answer": "494 + 494 = 988"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAD = BABY", "Answer": "757 + 757 = 1514"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAD = BODY", "Answer": "787 + 787 = 1574"}
{"Question": "EYE + EYE = ARMY", "Answer": "868 + 868 = 1736"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAD = BACK", "Answer": "878 + 878 = 1756"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAD = IDEA", "Answer": "989 + 989 = 1978"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAY = EYE", "Answer": "161 + 162 = 323"}
{"Question": "POP + POT = TOOL", "Answer": "505 + 501 = 1006"}
{"Question": "POP + POT = ODDS", "Answer": "616 + 613 = 1229"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAY = BALL", "Answer": "626 + 629 = 1255"}
{"Question": "POP + POT = DATA", "Answer": "686 + 687 = 1373"}
{"Question": "POP + POT = TOSS", "Answer": "747 + 741 = 1488"}
{"Question": "POP + POT = ONTO", "Answer": "818 + 813 = 1631"}
{"Question": "DAD + DAY = EASE", "Answer": "878 + 873 = 1751"}
{"Question": "EYE + EGG = GAY", "Answer": "131 + 122 = 253"}
{"Question": "DAD + DNA = ALL", "Answer": "373 + 327 = 700"}
{"Question": "DAD + DNA = NAME", "Answer": "626 + 612 = 1238"}
{"Question": "DAD + DNA = BALL", "Answer": "757 + 765 = 1522"}
{"Question": "DAD + DNA = EDGE", "Answer": "929 + 972 = 1901"}
{"Question": "EYE + EGG = YEAH", "Answer": "919 + 988 = 1907"}
{"Question": "EYE + EAR = AREA", "Answer": "757 + 714 = 1471"}
{"Question": "DAD + DRY = EVER", "Answer": "747 + 769 = 1516"}
{"Question": "EYE + ERA = ALLY", "Answer": "909 + 971 = 1880"}
{"Question": "POP + PER = ROPE", "Answer": "989 + 901 = 1890"}
{"Question": "MOM + MAD = ODDS", "Answer": "919 + 968 = 1887"}
{"Question": "EYE + ETC = TENT", "Answer": "989 + 912 = 1901"}
{"Question": "POP + COP = POOL", "Answer": "101 + 901 = 1002"}
{"Question": "DAD + MAD = AIM", "Answer": "131 + 231 = 362"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAD = DEEP", "Answer": "151 + 851 = 1002"}
{"Question": "POP + COP = PASS", "Answer": "161 + 861 = 1022"}
{"Question": "DAD + SAD = ASK", "Answer": "181 + 681 = 862"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAD = DEBT", "Answer": "191 + 891 = 1082"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAD = AIDE", "Answer": "212 + 812 = 1024"}
{"Question": "POP + TOP = DATA", "Answer": "676 + 576 = 1252"}
{"Question": "DAD + MAD = FARM", "Answer": "848 + 648 = 1496"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAD = BEAN", "Answer": "898 + 198 = 1096"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAD = BABY", "Answer": "909 + 109 = 1018"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAD = BODY", "Answer": "949 + 149 = 1098"}
{"Question": "POP + TOO = PEER", "Answer": "151 + 855 = 1006"}
{"Question": "MOM + TOO = MEAT", "Answer": "171 + 877 = 1048"}
{"Question": "SEE + YES = EAST", "Answer": "211 + 812 = 1023"}
{"Question": "SEE + YES = AREA", "Answer": "299 + 792 = 1091"}
{"Question": "TOO + HOT = DATA", "Answer": "577 + 675 = 1252"}
{"Question": "TOO + LOT = ALL", "Answer": "655 + 156 = 811"}
{"Question": "MOM + TOO = BOSS", "Answer": "767 + 866 = 1633"}
{"Question": "EGG + AGE = ARAB", "Answer": "855 + 158 = 1013"}
{"Question": "MOM + TOO = NONE", "Answer": "858 + 655 = 1513"}
{"Question": "MOM + TOO = TALL", "Answer": "878 + 177 = 1055"}
{"Question": "TOO + LOT = BALL", "Answer": "877 + 578 = 1455"}
{"Question": "MOM + TOO = TENT", "Answer": "929 + 122 = 1051"}
{"Question": "MOM + TOO = TIME", "Answer": "949 + 144 = 1093"}
{"Question": "MOM + POP = MEET", "Answer": "151 + 858 = 1009"}
{"Question": "NET + TEN = NOTE", "Answer": "198 + 891 = 1089"}
{"Question": "MOM + DOG = MOOD", "Answer": "101 + 908 = 1009"}
{"Question": "MOM + HOT = MATH", "Answer": "141 + 948 = 1089"}
{"Question": "DAD + PAN = DEEP", "Answer": "151 + 857 = 1008"}
{"Question": "AID + DIE = DEAD", "Answer": "891 + 190 = 1081"}
{"Question": "MOM + LOT = MALL", "Answer": "191 + 897 = 1088"}
{"Question": "DAD + EAR = AIDE", "Answer": "212 + 816 = 1028"}
{"Question": "SON + NOD = ODDS", "Answer": "715 + 512 = 1227"}
{"Question": "POP + TOE = MEET", "Answer": "525 + 924 = 1449"}
{"Question": "DAD + EAR = FREE", "Answer": "545 + 843 = 1388"}
{"Question": "DAD + BAR = AREA", "Answer": "616 + 915 = 1531"}
{"Question": "HAT + TAP = PATH", "Answer": "736 + 631 = 1367"}
{"Question": "DAD + EAT = AREA", "Answer": "717 + 314 = 1031"}
{"Question": "DAD + EAR = RACE", "Answer": "767 + 861 = 1628"}
{"Question": "BAG + GAP = DATA", "Answer": "867 + 769 = 1636"}
{"Question": "ARM + MRS = STAR", "Answer": "687 + 781 = 1468"}
{"Question": "SET + TEA = EAST", "Answer": "218 + 810 = 1028"}
{"Question": "DAD + EAR = CARE", "Answer": "838 + 537 = 1375"}
{"Question": "END + DNA = EVEN", "Answer": "158 + 857 = 1015"}
{"Question": "DAD + TAX = TEXT", "Answer": "868 + 163 = 1031"}
{"Question": "DAD + TAP = THAT", "Answer": "898 + 193 = 1091"}
{"Question": "DAD + EAR = AREA", "Answer": "919 + 312 = 1231"}
{"Question": "DNA + ANY = DEAD", "Answer": "149 + 942 = 1091"}
{"Question": "BET + TEA = BITE", "Answer": "149 + 945 = 1094"}
{"Question": "EYE + ONE = EVEN", "Answer": "191 + 821 = 1012"}
{"Question": "EYE + SHE = EASY", "Answer": "121 + 971 = 1092"}
{"Question": "EYE + LIE = ILL", "Answer": "181 + 241 = 422"}
{"Question": "DAD + OLD = ALSO", "Answer": "414 + 824 = 1238"}
{"Question": "DAD + END = AIDE", "Answer": "414 + 834 = 1248"}
{"Question": "EYE + AGE = YELL", "Answer": "515 + 985 = 1500"}
{"Question": "DAD + END = RARE", "Answer": "727 + 487 = 1214"}
{"Question": "POP + CAP = COOK", "Answer": "808 + 198 = 1006"}
{"Question": "EYE + AGE = ALLY", "Answer": "868 + 138 = 1006"}
{"Question": "EYE + TIE = DIET", "Answer": "838 + 648 = 1486"}
{"Question": "DAD + END = EVEN", "Answer": "848 + 168 = 1016"}
{"Question": "DAD + BED = BALL", "Answer": "909 + 179 = 1088"}
{"Question": "EYE + THE = THEY", "Answer": "989 + 109 = 1098"}
{"Question": "POP + CEO = PACE", "Answer": "141 + 954 = 1095"}
{"Question": "EYE + ANY = EVEN", "Answer": "151 + 865 = 1016"}
{"Question": "MOM + TWO = MEET", "Answer": "171 + 837 = 1008"}
{"Question": "POP + EGG = PIPE", "Answer": "141 + 877 = 1018"}
{"Question": "NET + THE = THEN", "Answer": "981 + 108 = 1089"}
{"Question": "EYE + FLY = LESS", "Answer": "282 + 918 = 1200"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEA = EDGE", "Answer": "383 + 918 = 1301"}
{"Question": "MRS + SIR = MERE", "Answer": "128 + 892 = 1020"}
{"Question": "DAD + TEA = THAT", "Answer": "838 + 193 = 1031"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEA = EASE", "Answer": "838 + 513 = 1351"}
{"Question": "DAD + ERA = EVER", "Answer": "868 + 146 = 1014"}
{"Question": "DAD + SEA = SEEK", "Answer": "898 + 109 = 1007"}
{"Question": "DAD + TEA = TREE", "Answer": "898 + 179 = 1077"}
{"Question": "ADD + ERA = DOOR", "Answer": "911 + 309 = 1220"}
{"Question": "DAD + TEA = TENT", "Answer": "929 + 102 = 1031"}
{"Question": "EYE + ANY = AREA", "Answer": "929 + 162 = 1091"}
{"Question": "EYE + CRY = CREW", "Answer": "989 + 108 = 1097"}
{"Question": "NOT + TEN = NINE", "Answer": "128 + 891 = 1019"}
{"Question": "AGE + ERA = GANG", "Answer": "219 + 982 = 1201"}
{"Question": "MOM + TEN = ONTO", "Answer": "616 + 975 = 1591"}
{"Question": "EYE + TOP = POET", "Answer": "727 + 851 = 1578"}
{"Question": "MOM + BAD = BOMB", "Answer": "909 + 182 = 1091"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALL = IDEA", "Answer": "688 + 688 = 1376"}
{"Question": "TOO + TOO = NONE", "Answer": "755 + 755 = 1510"}
{"Question": "ADD + ADD = BEAN", "Answer": "788 + 788 = 1576"}
{"Question": "ALL + ALL = BLOW", "Answer": "877 + 877 = 1754"}
{"Question": "EGG + EGG = HUGE", "Answer": "899 + 899 = 1798"}
{"Question": "ADD + ADD = BABY", "Answer": "955 + 955 = 1910"}
{"Question": "FEE + FEW = OFF", "Answer": "155 + 156 = 311"}
{"Question": "SEE + SEA = ASK", "Answer": "211 + 214 = 425"}
{"Question": "SEE + SEA = ADD", "Answer": "488 + 489 = 977"}
{"Question": "TOO + TOE = POET", "Answer": "622 + 624 = 1246"}
{"Question": "SEE + SEA = BOSS", "Answer": "788 + 789 = 1577"}
{"Question": "FEE + FEW = AWAY", "Answer": "855 + 857 = 1712"}
{"Question": "SEE + SEA = BALL", "Answer": "866 + 867 = 1733"}
{"Question": "TOO + TOP = POET", "Answer": "877 + 871 = 1748"}
{"Question": "ADD + AID = ILL", "Answer": "388 + 378 = 766"}
{"Question": "ODD + OLD = TOO", "Answer": "477 + 467 = 944"}
{"Question": "TOO + TWO = AWAY", "Answer": "677 + 637 = 1314"}
{"Question": "SEE + SHE = BOSS", "Answer": "688 + 678 = 1366"}
{"Question": "ADD + AID = BILL", "Answer": "766 + 756 = 1522"}
{"Question": "TOO + TWO = NONE", "Answer": "877 + 837 = 1714"}
{"Question": "ADD + AND = NAME", "Answer": "988 + 918 = 1906"}
{"Question": "SEA + SAY = EYE", "Answer": "375 + 352 = 727"}
{"Question": "ADD + AGE = DEAD", "Answer": "511 + 540 = 1051"}
{"Question": "ALL + AGO = GOAL", "Answer": "544 + 510 = 1054"}
{"Question": "EGG + EAR = CARE", "Answer": "577 + 508 = 1085"}
{"Question": "CAR + CRY = AREA", "Answer": "612 + 629 = 1241"}
{"Question": "SKI + SIN = NINE", "Answer": "683 + 631 = 1314"}
{"Question": "EGG + EAR = RACE", "Answer": "655 + 621 = 1276"}
{"Question": "ODD + ONE = TEEN", "Answer": "655 + 683 = 1338"}
{"Question": "EGG + EAT = RARE", "Answer": "677 + 639 = 1316"}
{"Question": "EGG + EAR = FLEE", "Answer": "677 + 689 = 1366"}
{"Question": "TOO + TEN = NONE", "Answer": "755 + 761 = 1516"}
{"Question": "EGG + EAR = RARE", "Answer": "766 + 751 = 1517"}
{"Question": "EGG + EAT = GATE", "Answer": "811 + 867 = 1678"}
{"Question": "SEE + SAD = ODDS", "Answer": "822 + 846 = 1668"}
{"Question": "ODD + ONE = EVEN", "Answer": "855 + 861 = 1716"}
{"Question": "EGG + EAT = DATA", "Answer": "855 + 872 = 1727"}
{"Question": "SEA + SAD = EASE", "Answer": "816 + 865 = 1681"}
{"Question": "SEE + SAD = DATA", "Answer": "866 + 871 = 1737"}
{"Question": "ILL + ITS = ELSE", "Answer": "877 + 864 = 1741"}
{"Question": "SEE + SAD = EASE", "Answer": "911 + 980 = 1891"}
{"Question": "ADD + ACT = CALL", "Answer": "988 + 912 = 1900"}
{"Question": "ADD + AGE = GANG", "Answer": "988 + 913 = 1901"}
{"Question": "TOO + DOG = DATA", "Answer": "944 + 146 = 1090"}
{"Question": "TOO + NOD = TENT", "Answer": "144 + 947 = 1091"}
{"Question": "FEE + CEO = FACT", "Answer": "144 + 948 = 1092"}
{"Question": "FEE + TEA = FOOT", "Answer": "155 + 853 = 1008"}
{"Question": "FEE + BED = FALL", "Answer": "166 + 867 = 1033"}
{"Question": "FEE + TEA = FATE", "Answer": "199 + 890 = 1089"}
{"Question": "EGG + AGO = EDGE", "Answer": "199 + 892 = 1091"}
{"Question": "SEE + TEA = EASE", "Answer": "211 + 810 = 1021"}
{"Question": "ALL + FLY = LEAF", "Answer": "211 + 817 = 1028"}
{"Question": "FEE + YES = EASY", "Answer": "711 + 312 = 1023"}
{"Question": "FEE + DIE = FOOD", "Answer": "144 + 864 = 1008"}
{"Question": "ADD + BED = ARAB", "Answer": "144 + 874 = 1018"}
{"Question": "ADD + END = ABLE", "Answer": "144 + 894 = 1038"}
{"Question": "EGG + DOG = ODD", "Answer": "177 + 467 = 644"}
{"Question": "ADD + NOD = DNA", "Answer": "688 + 128 = 816"}
{"Question": "FEE + LIE = FILM", "Answer": "188 + 908 = 1096"}
{"Question": "FEE + TOE = FOOT", "Answer": "199 + 809 = 1008"}
{"Question": "ADD + RED = DOOR", "Answer": "711 + 291 = 1002"}
{"Question": "ADD + GOD = DRAG", "Answer": "811 + 271 = 1082"}
{"Question": "TOO + WHO = HOW", "Answer": "288 + 698 = 986"}
{"Question": "ADD + OLD = DEAL", "Answer": "311 + 721 = 1032"}
{"Question": "EGG + ALL = EDGE", "Answer": "122 + 899 = 1021"}
{"Question": "ALL + END = AIDE", "Answer": "122 + 957 = 1079"}
{"Question": "TOO + YES = TEST", "Answer": "155 + 906 = 1061"}
{"Question": "TOO + DAY = DATA", "Answer": "988 + 102 = 1090"}
{"Question": "EGG + SAD = EASE", "Answer": "188 + 903 = 1091"}
{"Question": "ILL + EAR = RARE", "Answer": "577 + 841 = 1418"}
{"Question": "ERA + ERA = ADD", "Answer": "183 + 183 = 366"}
{"Question": "ERA + ERA = DAD", "Answer": "237 + 237 = 474"}
{"Question": "BAD + BAD = ADD", "Answer": "250 + 250 = 500"}
{"Question": "BAG + BAG = ADD", "Answer": "372 + 372 = 744"}
{"Question": "BED + BED = DEEP", "Answer": "501 + 501 = 1002"}
{"Question": "AGE + AGE = GENE", "Answer": "510 + 510 = 1020"}
{"Question": "ARM + ARM = MERE", "Answer": "601 + 601 = 1202"}
{"Question": "AND + AND = NEED", "Answer": "610 + 610 = 1220"}
{"Question": "AGO + AGO = GOOD", "Answer": "612 + 612 = 1224"}
{"Question": "DNA + DNA = NEED", "Answer": "613 + 613 = 1226"}
{"Question": "ACT + ACT = COOK", "Answer": "614 + 614 = 1228"}
{"Question": "BAD + BAD = DATA", "Answer": "621 + 621 = 1242"}
{"Question": "BED + BED = DATA", "Answer": "641 + 641 = 1282"}
{"Question": "EAR + EAR = FREE", "Answer": "683 + 683 = 1366"}
{"Question": "AGE + AGE = BEER", "Answer": "724 + 724 = 1448"}
{"Question": "BAG + BAG = DATA", "Answer": "742 + 742 = 1484"}
{"Question": "GAS + GAS = MASS", "Answer": "750 + 750 = 1500"}
{"Question": "DAY + DAY = FEED", "Answer": "834 + 834 = 1668"}
{"Question": "TEN + TEN = DATA", "Answer": "843 + 843 = 1686"}
{"Question": "AID + AID = BILL", "Answer": "872 + 872 = 1744"}
{"Question": "EAR + EAR = CARE", "Answer": "874 + 874 = 1748"}
{"Question": "EAR + EAR = FLEE", "Answer": "894 + 894 = 1788"}
{"Question": "BET + BET = DATA", "Answer": "924 + 924 = 1848"}
{"Question": "AND + AND = MOON", "Answer": "942 + 942 = 1884"}
{"Question": "ITS + ITS = KISS", "Answer": "950 + 950 = 1900"}
{"Question": "ACT + ACT = TALL", "Answer": "961 + 961 = 1922"}
{"Question": "LOT + LOW = TOOL", "Answer": "501 + 504 = 1005"}
{"Question": "BED + BET = DATA", "Answer": "541 + 549 = 1090"}
{"Question": "SIT + SIN = INTO", "Answer": "712 + 714 = 1426"}
{"Question": "AIM + AID = IDEA", "Answer": "713 + 714 = 1427"}
{"Question": "AGE + AGO = BEER", "Answer": "724 + 725 = 1449"}
{"Question": "EAR + EAT = DATE", "Answer": "748 + 749 = 1497"}
{"Question": "BAN + BAG = GANG", "Answer": "750 + 751 = 1501"}
{"Question": "LAB + LAP = BABY", "Answer": "751 + 759 = 1510"}
{"Question": "PET + PER = TRUE", "Answer": "761 + 765 = 1526"}
{"Question": "TEN + TEA = PANT", "Answer": "762 + 765 = 1527"}
{"Question": "EAT + EAR = TREE", "Answer": "891 + 897 = 1788"}
{"Question": "BAG + BAR = GRAB", "Answer": "901 + 908 = 1809"}
{"Question": "DIG + DIE = EDGE", "Answer": "950 + 951 = 1901"}
{"Question": "AID + AND = IDEA", "Answer": "613 + 693 = 1306"}
{"Question": "CAT + CUT = AUTO", "Answer": "716 + 746 = 1462"}
{"Question": "BED + BAD = DARE", "Answer": "721 + 741 = 1462"}
{"Question": "BAD + BED = DEBT", "Answer": "731 + 741 = 1472"}
{"Question": "BAG + BIG = DATA", "Answer": "742 + 752 = 1494"}
{"Question": "BET + BUT = TUBE", "Answer": "821 + 861 = 1682"}
{"Question": "ONE + OWE = TEEN", "Answer": "826 + 836 = 1662"}
{"Question": "ACT + ART = CALL", "Answer": "915 + 985 = 1900"}
{"Question": "EAR + END = RARE", "Answer": "631 + 685 = 1316"}
{"Question": "TEN + TWO = NONE", "Answer": "641 + 673 = 1314"}
{"Question": "SAD + SIN = AIDS", "Answer": "715 + 742 = 1457"}
{"Question": "AGE + ART = TEAR", "Answer": "724 + 751 = 1475"}
{"Question": "DNA + DIE = NEED", "Answer": "812 + 856 = 1668"}
{"Question": "DIE + TIE = DATA", "Answer": "145 + 945 = 1090"}
{"Question": "BET + NET = BONE", "Answer": "147 + 947 = 1094"}
{"Question": "BAD + MAD = BOOM", "Answer": "154 + 854 = 1008"}
{"Question": "BET + YET = BABY", "Answer": "159 + 859 = 1018"}
{"Question": "BAD + MAD = BELL", "Answer": "172 + 872 = 1044"}
{"Question": "AND + END = AIDE", "Answer": "174 + 874 = 1048"}
{"Question": "BAD + SAD = BOSS", "Answer": "194 + 894 = 1088"}
{"Question": "FOR + NOR = ROOF", "Answer": "201 + 801 = 1002"}
{"Question": "DAY + SAY = AIDS", "Answer": "214 + 814 = 1028"}
{"Question": "EAR + CAR = RICE", "Answer": "241 + 841 = 1082"}
{"Question": "DIG + BIG = GOOD", "Answer": "251 + 751 = 1002"}
{"Question": "EAT + CAT = TREE", "Answer": "261 + 761 = 1022"}
{"Question": "TAP + CAP = ACT", "Answer": "271 + 471 = 742"}
{"Question": "BAR + EAR = FREE", "Answer": "594 + 894 = 1488"}
{"Question": "EAR + WAR = CREW", "Answer": "634 + 834 = 1468"}
{"Question": "BAN + DAY = BEND", "Answer": "124 + 925 = 1049"}
{"Question": "GUN + BUS = GENE", "Answer": "163 + 867 = 1030"}
{"Question": "LAB + CAN = ABLE", "Answer": "312 + 918 = 1230"}
{"Question": "AID + SIN = ODDS", "Answer": "462 + 765 = 1227"}
{"Question": "BED + TEA = DATE", "Answer": "541 + 843 = 1384"}
{"Question": "HER + AIR = HERE", "Answer": "105 + 945 = 1050"}
{"Question": "DAY + TOY = DATA", "Answer": "105 + 985 = 1090"}
{"Question": "CAT + OUT = AUTO", "Answer": "514 + 834 = 1348"}
